[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Where was first and only Modern Olympic games of 1800s played?",
    "option1": "Athens, Greece",
    "option2": "London, Great Britain",
    "option3": "Paris, France",
    "option4": "St. Louis, United States",
    "answer": "Athens, Greece"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Who has the most Olympic medals (23) ever?",
    "option1": "Boris Shakhlin",
    "option2": "Michael Phelps",
    "option3": "Nikolai Andrianov",
    "option4": "Ole Einar Bjørndalen",
    "answer": "Michael Phelps"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Most Olympic medals (18) by woman?",
    "option1": "Birgit Fischer",
    "option2": "Dana Torres",
    "option3": "Jenny Thompson",
    "option4": "Larisa Latynina",
    "answer": "Larisa Latynina"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Most Olympic golds by man",
    "option1": "Boris Shakhlin",
    "option2": "Michael Phelps",
    "option3": "Nikolai Andrianov",
    "option4": "Ole Einar Bjørndalen",
    "answer": "Michael Phelps"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Most Olympic golds by woman",
    "option1": "Birgit Fischer",
    "option2": "Dana Torres",
    "option3": "Jenny Thompson",
    "option4": "Larisa Latynina",
    "answer": "Larisa Latynina"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Most golds by woman in single Olympics (6)",
    "option1": "Agnes Keleti",
    "option2": "Fanny Blankers-Koen",
    "option3": "Kristin Otto",
    "option4": "Larisa Latynina",
    "answer": "Kristin Otto"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Fastest 100 m runner in 9.58 seconds",
    "option1": "Donovan Bailey",
    "option2": "Richard Thompson",
    "option3": "Tyson Gay",
    "option4": "Usain Bolt",
    "answer": "Usain Bolt"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Fastest 100 m female runner in 10.49 seconds",
    "option1": "Christine Arron",
    "option2": "Florence Griffith-Joyner",
    "option3": "Irina Privalova",
    "option4": "Shelly-Ann Fraser-Pryce",
    "answer": "Florence Griffith-Joyner"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Most titles won in men's Olympic football (3)",
    "option1": "Argentina and Uruguay",
    "option2": "Cameroon and Nigeria",
    "option3": "France and Italy",
    "option4": "Great Britain and Hungary",
    "answer": "Great Britain and Hungary"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Most titles won in Olympic football both men's and women's combined (4)",
    "option1": "Argentina",
    "option2": "Great Britain",
    "option3": "Hungary",
    "option4": "United States",
    "answer": "United States"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "When did Modern Olympics start?",
    "option1": "1895 AD",
    "option2": "1896 AD",
    "option3": "1897 AD",
    "option4": "1898 AD",
    "answer": "1896 AD"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "Which is not an Olympic sport?",
    "option1": "Swimming",
    "option2": "High Jump",
    "option3": "Skateboarding",
    "option4": "Wrestling",
    "answer": "Skateboarding"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "Which is not an Olympic sport?",
    "option1": "Basketball",
    "option2": "Cricket",
    "option3": "Football",
    "option4": "Tennis",
    "answer": "Cricket"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Where is Olympia, the place where ancient Olympic games were staged?",
    "option1": "Great Britain",
    "option2": "Greece",
    "option3": "Italy",
    "option4": "Syria",
    "answer": "Greece"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "Number of rings in Olympic flag",
    "option1": 5,
    "option2": 6,
    "option3": 7,
    "option4": 8,
    "answer": 5
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "Country with most summer Olympic medals",
    "option1": "Germany",
    "option2": "Great Britain",
    "option3": "Russia",
    "option4": "United States",
    "answer": "United States"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "Country with most winter Olympic medals",
    "option1": "Germany",
    "option2": "Great Britain",
    "option3": "Russia",
    "option4": "United States",
    "answer": "Germany"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "Who never scored ICC ODI world cup final century?",
    "option1": "Adam Gilchrist",
    "option2": "Mahela Jayawardene",
    "option3": "Sachin Tendulkar",
    "option4": "Viv Richards",
    "answer": "Sachin Tendulkar"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Cricketer with most runs in both Test and ODI",
    "option1": "Jacques Kallis",
    "option2": "Kumar Sangakkara",
    "option3": "Ricky Ponting",
    "option4": "Sachin Tendulkar",
    "answer": "Sachin Tendulkar"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "Cricketer with most wickets in both Test and ODI",
    "option1": "Glenn McGrath",
    "option2": "Muttiah Muralitharan",
    "option3": "Shaun Pollock",
    "option4": "Wasim Akram",
    "answer": "Muttiah Muralitharan"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "Who is known as best cricketer ever widely because of batting average of 99.94 while others don't even come close to 70.00?",
    "option1": "Donald Bradman",
    "option2": "Garfield Sobers",
    "option3": "Sachin Tendulkar",
    "option4": "Muttiah Muralitharan",
    "answer": "Donald Bradman"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "Which of these Australian players haven't won 3 ICC ODI cricket world cups?",
    "option1": "Adam Gilchrist",
    "option2": "Glenn McGrath",
    "option3": "Matthew Hayden",
    "option4": "Ricky Ponting",
    "answer": "Matthew Hayden"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "Which two countries contest in the test series \"The Ashes\"?",
    "option1": "Australia and England",
    "option2": "India and Pakistan",
    "option3": "South Africa and Zimbabwe",
    "option4": "None of these",
    "answer": "Australia and England"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "Who is known as \"Sultan of Swing\"?",
    "option1": "Chaminda Vaas",
    "option2": "Irfan Pathan",
    "option3": "Mustafizur Rahman",
    "option4": "Wasim Akram",
    "answer": "Wasim Akram"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "Which Pakistani bowler called \"The Rawalpindi Express\" bowled the fastest recorded delivery ever at 161.3 km/hr?",
    "option1": "Imran Khan",
    "option2": "Shoaib Akhtar",
    "option3": "Umar Gul",
    "option4": "Waqar Younis",
    "answer": "Shoaib Akhtar"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "Cricketer with most First Class runs",
    "option1": "Jack Hobbs",
    "option2": "Herbert Sutcliffe",
    "option3": "Wally Hammond",
    "option4": "William Gilbert Grace",
    "answer": "Jack Hobbs"
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "Most matches as captain in all cricket formats",
    "option1": "Graeme Smith",
    "option2": "Mahendra Singh Dhoni",
    "option3": "Ricky Ponting",
    "option4": "Stephen Fleming",
    "answer": "Mahendra Singh Dhoni"
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "Player with most ODI double hundreds (3)",
    "option1": "Chris Gayle",
    "option2": "Fakhar Zaman",
    "option3": "Martin Guptill",
    "option4": "Rohit Sharma",
    "answer": "Rohit Sharma"
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "Which two players created biggest partnership in an inning (372) in ODI history?",
    "option1": "Chris Gayle and Marlon Samuels",
    "option2": "Imam-ul-Haq and Fakhar Zaman",
    "option3": "Sachin Tendulkar and Rahul Dravid",
    "option4": "Upul Tharanga and Sanath Jayasuriya",
    "answer": "Chris Gayle and Marlon Samuels"
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "Which two players created biggest partnership in an inning (624) in Test history?",
    "option1": "Andrew Jones and Martin Crowe",
    "option2": "Bill Ponsford and Donald Bradman",
    "option3": "Kumar Sangakkara and Mahela Jayawardene",
    "option4": "Mudassar Nazar and Javed Miandad",
    "answer": "Kumar Sangakkara and Mahela Jayawardene"
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "For which franchise does Nepal only player in IPL Sandeep Lamichhane play?",
    "option1": "Delhi Capitals",
    "option2": "Kings XI Punjab",
    "option3": "Kolkata Knight Riders",
    "option4": "Rajasthan Royals",
    "answer": "Delhi Capitals"
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "Which of these places' franchises did not win Champions League T20?",
    "option1": "Chennai",
    "option2": "Mumbai",
    "option3": "Sydney",
    "option4": "Trinidad and Tobago",
    "answer": "Trinidad and Tobago"
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "Who was nicknamed the Siberian Siren for grunting when they hit the ball?",
    "option1": "Anna Kournikova",
    "option2": "Maria Sharapova",
    "option3": "Svetlana Kuznetsova",
    "option4": "Vera Zvonareva",
    "answer": "Maria Sharapova"
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "question": "Which player among Big Four in tennis has achieved the least in career?",
    "option1": "Andy Murray",
    "option2": "Novak Djokovic",
    "option3": "Rafael Nadal",
    "option4": "Roger Federer",
    "answer": "Andy Murray"
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "question": "Which is the only female tennis player to beat male opponent in \"Battle of the Sexes\"?",
    "option1": "Margaret Court",
    "option2": "Billie Jean King",
    "option3": "Martina Navratilova",
    "option4": "Serena Williams",
    "answer": "Billie Jean King"
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "question": "Who is the only player to win 3 FIFA world cups as a player?",
    "option1": "Giovanni Ferrari",
    "option2": "Giuseppe Meazza",
    "option3": "Pele",
    "option4": "Ronaldo",
    "answer": "Pele"
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "question": "Which was the last country to win FIFA world cup in home soil?",
    "option1": "England",
    "option2": "France",
    "option3": "Germany",
    "option4": "Italy",
    "answer": "France"
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "question": "Which among these teams never won UEFA European cup or Champions League 3 times in a row?",
    "option1": "AC Milan",
    "option2": "Ajax",
    "option3": "Bayern Munich",
    "option4": "Real Madrid",
    "answer": "AC Milan"
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "question": "Derby della Madonnina is played between",
    "option1": "Atletico Madrid and Real Madrid",
    "option2": "AC Milan and Inter Milan",
    "option3": "Bayern Munich and 1860 Munich",
    "option4": "None of these",
    "answer": "AC Milan and Inter Milan"
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "question": "Which player has scored most goals (13) in a single FIFA world cup tournament?",
    "option1": "Gerd Muller (Germany)",
    "option2": "Just Fontaine (France)",
    "option3": "Ronaldo (Brazil)",
    "option4": "Sandor Kocsis (Hungary)",
    "answer": "Just Fontaine (France)"
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "question": "How many times has Germany won the FIFA world cup after reunification?",
    "option1": 3,
    "option2": 2,
    "option3": 1,
    "option4": "None of these",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "question": "Which club other than Barcelona has won more Copa Del Reys than Real Madrid?",
    "option1": "Atletico Madrid",
    "option2": "Athletic Bilbao",
    "option3": "Sevilla",
    "option4": "Valencia",
    "answer": "Athletic Bilbao"
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "question": "Which spanish club only plays with local players?",
    "option1": "Atletico Madrid",
    "option2": "Athletic Bilbao",
    "option3": "Sevilla",
    "option4": "Valencia",
    "answer": "Athletic Bilbao"
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "question": "Only African player to win Ballon d'or",
    "option1": "Abedi Pele (Ghana)",
    "option2": "George Weah (Liberia)",
    "option3": "Nwankwo Kanu (Nigeria)",
    "option4": "Roger Milla (Cameroon)",
    "answer": "George Weah (Liberia)"
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "question": "Nation to lose most FIFA world cup finals (4)",
    "option1": "Argentina",
    "option2": "Brazil",
    "option3": "Germany",
    "option4": "Netherlands",
    "answer": "Germany"
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "question": "Only goalkeeper to win Ballon d'or",
    "option1": "Gordon Banks",
    "option2": "Lev Yashin",
    "option3": "Oliver Kahn",
    "option4": "Sepp Maier",
    "answer": "Lev Yashin"
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "question": "Michael Jordon played for which of the following teams?",
    "option1": "Boston Celtics",
    "option2": "Chicago Bulls",
    "option3": "Golden State Warriors",
    "option4": "LA Lakers",
    "answer": "Chicago Bulls"
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "question": "Which team has won the most NBA titles (17)?",
    "option1": "Boston Celtics",
    "option2": "Chicago Bulls",
    "option3": "Golden State Warriors",
    "option4": "LA Lakers",
    "answer": "Boston Celtics"
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "question": "Babe Ruth left which baseball team to play for NY Yankees?",
    "option1": "Boston Red Sox",
    "option2": "Chicago Cubs",
    "option3": "Detroit Tigers",
    "option4": "St. Louis Cardinals",
    "answer": "Boston Red Sox"
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "question": "Wayne Gretzky is associated with which sport?",
    "option1": "American Football",
    "option2": "Field Hockey",
    "option3": "Golf",
    "option4": "Ice Hockey",
    "answer": "Ice Hockey"
  }
]